#### Contact

+48 579123910 (Mobile) brijeshkumarmaisuriya@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/brijeshmaisuriya-516164238 (LinkedIn) github.com/brijeshmaster (Other)

#### Top Skills

React.js JavaScript Tailwind CSS

# **BRIJESH MAISURIYA**

React Developer & B2B

Opole, Opolskie, Poland

### Summary

Innovative Experience React Developer building and maintaining responsive website and Highly skilled software development professional bringing enormous talents for software design, development and integration. Offering advanced knowledge of indemand programming languages. Background writing code and developing systems for React development applications. expert in React.js,JavaScript,HTML5,CSS3,Rest API, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Next.js

## Experience

Freelancer.com
React Developer
August 2022 - Present (3 months)
Opole, Opolskie, Poland

- -A Freelancer developer is a self-employed professional who can design and code websites.
- -Developed websites using various frameworks and programming technologies including CSS3,HTML5,JAVASCRIPT,API,React,Node.js.
- -Collaborated and managed projects using Git.
- -Deployed and configured websites.
- -Designed REST calls using React to streamline user interface performance.
- -Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.
- -Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.

#### SEGAL LIMITED

React Developer

November 2021 - December 2021 (2 months)

Opole, Opolskie, Poland

- -Developed full-stack restaurant responsive modern design web application.
- -Discussed issues with team members to provide resolution and apply best practices.

-Maintained high-level expertise in React state management strategies.

Private Company
Junior Web Developer
March 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 6 months)
Surat Taluka, Gujarat, India

- -Developed wireframes, site maps and content inventories for new website designs.
- -Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with CSS,HTML, JavaScript,
- -Provided front-end website development using Bootstrap and other editing software.

Arbuda Instruments
Lead Software Engineer
March 2014 - February 2018 (4 years)
Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India

- -Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- -Administered, supported and monitored databases by proactively resolving database issues and maintaining servers.
- -Implemented security measures to protect vital business data.
- -Created and updated database designs and data models.

Galaxy Technologies Internship Trainee August 2013 - March 2014 (8 months)

Surat, Gujarat, India

- -Created powerful Collage Management Systems to serve as interface for client in ASP.NET Technologies
- -Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS for integration and cross-browser compatibility.
- -Analyzed, evaluated and developed new web and database applications.
- -Participated in highly complex projects with customers, managers and endusers.

Tops computer Tech
Computer Science Tutor
November 2008 - March 2013 (4 years 5 months)
Surat, Gujarat, India

- -Evaluated and Teaching language like C++,C#,CSS,HTML,Javascript, Asp.net. complex coding methods and developed plan of action for achievement.
- -Conducted tutorial services for students to provide academic support and knowledge such as webdesign, planning and error solving in project of computer programming students .
- -Reviewed computer science class material with students to support discovery of correct answers to problems.

**NEO-SOFT Services** 

Internship Trainee

September 2008 - December 2008 (4 months)

Surat, Gujarat, India

- -Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects on time.
- -Developed ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM in visual basic.
- -Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement.

### Education

Politechnika Opolska

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Technology · (September 2018 - May 2022)

N.G.Patel Polytechnic, Isroli 637

Diploma of Education, Computer Engineering · (December 2005 - June 2008)